passionconnect.in 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy

## Passion Connect Technologies LLP Privacy Policy

The privacy policy is applicable to the websites of Passionconnect Technologies LLP (“Passionconnect”) including www.passionconnect.in, which also comprises of the mobile site, applications for iOS, Android, Windows operating system (all together referred to as “Site”). By browsing, visiting, accessing and/or using the services on this Site (or searching for any of the pages on this Site), you as customer consent and agree to our privacy policy laid out herein. You also agree that the information furnished by you is lawful, true and correct and does not violate or infringe any laws. In case of any violations, infringement, furnishing of wrongful or unauthorized information, Passionconnect shall not be liable for the same.

Please note that our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. Therefore, you may periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version of the privacy policy.

When you access our Site, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience and to give you better service. Further, your personal information is used to administer a promotion and contents on the Site. Also, to reply to queries of the various authorities in regard to your accessing of the Site and services availed by you.

When you access our Site, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

## Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

Our primary goal in doing so is to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience and to give you better service. Further, your personal information is used to administer a promotion and contents on the Site. Also, to reply to queries of the various authorities in regard to your accessing of the Site and services availed by you.

We’ve tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you’re not familiar with terms like cookies, IP addresses, pixel tags and browsers, then read about these key terms first. 

Your privacy matters to Passionconnect so whether you are new to Passionconnect or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions contact us...

## Information we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users like the people who matter most to you online to help analyse web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing our services.

  * **Information you give us.**

Our Service requires you to sign up for a Passionconnect account. When you do, we’ll ask for personal information, like your name, email address, telephone number or credit card.

  * **Information we get from your use of our services.**

We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, we may collect

    * **Device information** We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). Passionconnect may associate your device identifiers or phone number with your Passionconnect Account.

    * **Log information** When you use our services or view content provided by Passionconnect, we may automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

      1. Details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
      2. Telephony log information like your phone number, calling-party number, forwarding numbers, time and date of calls, duration of calls, SMS routing information and types of calls.
      3. Internet protocol address.
      4. Device event information such as crashes, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and referral URL.
      5. Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your Passionconnect Account.
    * **Location information** When you use a location-enabled service, we may collect and process information about your actual location, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers.

    * **Local storage** We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches.

    * **Cookies and anonymous identifiers** We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a Passionconnect service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Passionconnect features that may appear on other sites.

We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site. Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

By using the Site and/or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site in accordance with this privacy policy.

In accordance with Information Technology Act, 2000, if you wish to contact Passionconnect Technologies LLP about this privacy policy or privacy related issues via email, you may send an email to contact@passionconnect.in. Alternatively, you may send your concern via postal mail/courier at the following address:

Passionconnect Technologies LLP

# 729, 10th Main Road, 4th Block,  
Jayanagar, Bengaluru – 560 010 

**Kind Attn:**  
Chief Technology Officer

## How we use information we collect

### Collection of Your Personal Information

We collect information as part of operating our Websites and services.

At Passionconnect , we ask you to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address, or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites. If you choose to make a purchase or sign up for a paid subscription service, we will ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address.

In order to access some services, you will be asked to sign in with an e-mail address and password, which we refer to as your Passionconnect account. 

We collect additional information about your interaction with our sites and services without identifying you as an individual. For example, we receive certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses. We also might use Web site analytics tools on our sites to retrieve information from your browser, including the site you came from, the search engine(s) and the keywords you used to find our site, the pages you view within our site, your browser add-ons, and your browser's width and height.

When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from Passionconnect , we may use web beacons (described below), customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with Passionconnect, information collected through one Passionconnect service may be combined with information obtained through other Passionconnect services. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area.

### Use of Your Personal Information

Passionconnect collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and services. These uses include providing you with more effective customer service; making the sites or services easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and displaying content and advertising that are customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. Some Passionconnect services may send periodic member letters that are considered part of the service. Additionally, with your permission, we may also occasionally send you product surveys or promotional mailings to inform you of other products or services available from Passionconnect and its affiliates, and/or share your personal information with Passionconnect partners so they may send you information about their products and services. You can opt-out from receiving newsletters or promotional e-mail anytime by using this web form or by following the steps as described in the respective newsletter or promotional e-mail.

Personal information collected on Passionconnect sites and services may be stored and processed in India or any other country in which Passionconnect or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. 

### Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of Passionconnect and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent. Some sites allow you to choose to share your personal information with select Passionconnect partners so that they can contact you about their products, services or offers. Other sites, See the Communication Preferences section below for more information.

Some Passionconnect services are co-branded by Passionconnect and another company (partner). If you register to or use such a service, both a Passionconnect privacy statement and the partner’s privacy statement may be displayed. If so, both Passionconnect and the partner will receive information you provide such as on registration forms.

Passionconnect occasionally hires other companies (vendor) to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those service providers will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose than for delivering the service to Passionconnect in accordance with Passionconnect’s instructions and policies. However, our vendors may use aggregate data for fraud detection to help improve their services. This helps them to more accurately detect fraudulent transactions. We may access or disclose information about you, including the content of your communications, in order to: (a) comply with the law or respond to lawful requests or legal process; (b) protect the rights or property of Passionconnect or our customers, including the enforcement of our agreements or policies governing your use of the services; or (c) act on a good faith belief that such access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of Passionconnect employees, customers or the public. We may also disclose personal information as part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets.

### Accessing and updating your personal information

Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

We may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes).

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems.

  * **For external processing**

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

  * **For legal reasons**

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of Passionconnect if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

    * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
    * Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
    * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Passionconnect, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

If Passionconnect is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, we will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

## Information security

We work hard to protect Passionconnect and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

  * We encrypt many of our services using SSL
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
  * We restrict access to personal information to Passionconnect employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by. and its affiliates, including services offered on other sites (such as our advertising services), but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in search results, sites that may include Passionconnect services, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

## Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. We also adhere to several self regulatory frameworks. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

## Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

## Key Terms:- 

### Anonymous identifier

An anonymous identifier is a random string of characters that is used for the same purposes as a cookie on platforms, including certain mobile devices, where cookie technology is not available.

### Cookie

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.

### Passionconnect Account

You may access some of our services by signing up for a Passionconnect Account and providing us with some personal information (typically your name, email address and a password). This account information will be used to authenticate you when you access Passionconnect services and protect your account from unauthorized access by others. You can edit or terminate your account at any time through your Passionconnect Account settings.

### IP address

Every computer connected to the Internet is assigned a unique number known as an Internet protocol (IP) address. Since these numbers are usually assigned in country-based blocks, an IP address can often be used to identify the country from which a computer is connecting to the Internet.

### Non-personally identifiable information

This is information that is recorded about users so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user.

### Personal information

This is information which you provide to us which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by Passionconnect. 

## Sensitive personal information

This is a particular category of personal information relating to confidential medical facts, racial or ethnic origins, political or religious beliefs or sexuality.

## Server logs

Like most websites, our servers automatically record the page requests made when you visit our sites. These “server logs” typically include your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## Unique device identifier

A unique device identifier is a string of characters that is incorporated into a device by its manufacturer and can be used to uniquely identify that device. Different device identifiers vary in how permanent they are, whether they can be reset by users, and how they can be accessed. A given device may have several different unique device identifiers. Unique device identifiers can be used for various purposes, including security and fraud detection, syncing services such as a user’s email inbox, remembering the user’s preferences and providing relevant advertising.
